这些到底是什么鬼东西
What the shell are those things?
不管它们是什么
Whatever they were--
现在都成废铜烂铁了
they're junk now.
大伙儿
Guys,
斯普林特
Splinter.
我们必须找到斯普林特
We've got to find Splinter.
斯普林特老师
Master Splinter,
你能听见吗
can you hear me?
多纳泰罗
Donatello,
你有没有办法...
Donatello, any way to--
你在干什么
What are you doing?
龟壳电话
Shell cell.
我在呼叫斯普林特老师
I'm calling Master Splinter
希望能行
I hope.
哪个键是接听键?
which button do you press to answer this thing?
喂?
Hello?
斯普林特老师 你还好吗?
Master Splinter, are you all right?
有人吗?
Hello?
斯普林特老师...
Master Splinter...
愚蠢的设备
Stupid device.
你不用按任何按钮
you don't have to press any buttons.
已经接通了
You already answered it.
啊 李奥纳多
Ah. Leonardo,
不管那些机器是什么
whatever those mechanical menaces are,
它们已经啃穿了我们房子的支柱
they have managed to eat through the support structure of our home.
我们必须马上离开
We must leave right away.
在南端的老下水道枢纽处汇合
Meet me at the old drainage junction near South Point.
如果我们走南边的管道
If we take the south conduit,
它与旧的下水道有个交点
it'll intersect with the old drainage tunnel.
我们在那里与你会合 老师
We'll meet you there, Sensei.
他说什么? 他说什么了?
What'd he say? What'd he say?
提到我了吗?
Did he mention me?
再见 开裂的水管
Good-bye, broken pipe.
再见 脏兮兮的付费电话
Good-bye, grungy pay phone.
再见 凹陷的井盖
Good-bye, dented manhole cover.
再见了 我甜蜜的家
Good-bye, home, sweet home.
我来了 残酷的世界
Hello, cruel world.
走吧
Come on.
看来那些东西来过这儿了
Looks like those things have been through here.
这些墙已经严重受损
These walls are seriously compromised.
幸好屋顶还没塌下来
It's lucky this roof hasn't caved in.
你刚说什么?
You were saying?
没法前进 也没法后退
Can't go forward. Can't go back.
看来只能往上走了
Looks like we go up.
去地面可不是好主意
Hitting the surface is a bad idea.
我们没有选择了 李奥
We've got no other way to go, Leo.
好吧
All right,
但是我们只到下一个井盖就下去
but we're only going up to go down the next manhole.
明白吗? 不准乱逛
Got it? No fooling around.
记住老师说的话
Remember what Sensei said.
被人看到会很危险
It's dangerous for us to be seen,
更别说被抓住了
let alone captured.
我们需要保持隐蔽
We need to stay out of sight.
这话我们听了一千遍了 李奥
We got it the first thousand times, Leo.
跟着我走就是了
Just follow my lead.
李奥 快上去
Come on, Leo. Move it.
我可不想一直盯着你的屁股看
I don't want to be staring at your butt any longer than I have to.
嘘 各位
Shh. Guys!
啊 发现井盖
Ah, manhole cover,
十二点钟方向
12 o'clock.
又怎么了
Now what?
好极了 真是好极了
Great. Just great.
乌龟运气从不让人失望
The old turtle luck working true to form.
隐蔽得真好 拉夫
Way to be stealthy, Raph.
是的 新泽西都能听见你的动静了
Yeah. I don't think they heard you over in "Joisey."
搭把手
Give me a hand.
想都别想 米奇
Don't even think about it, Mikey.
哎 懒得理你们
Ah, forget you guys.
我自己推
I'll push it myself.
老兄 真是大丰收
Oh, man, what a score.
快躲起来 拉夫
Hide, Raph.
快点 赶紧
Come on. Hurry.
不好
No.
糟糕的选择 拉斐尔
Poor choice, Raphael.
你们看到那家伙的怂样了吗
Did you see the way that guy squirmed
我们抢他钱的时候
when we took his cash?
像待宰的羔羊
Sheep, man,
被我们这群狼狠狠地宰
sheep to be fleeced by us wolves.
哦 天哪
Oh, man.
想象一下他们打开车门的时候会有多惊讶
Imagine their surprise when they open the back of that truck.
这正是斯普林特老师所说的情况
This is exactly what Master Splinter was talking about.
我们必须把他救出来
We've got to get him out of there.
最后一个到屋顶的是笨蛋
Last one to the roof hatched from a rotten egg!
我们可以在第三和第一大道截住他们
We can cut them off at Third and First.
如果我们疯狂地跑的话
If we run like crazy.
难道有别的跑法吗
Is there any other way to run?
哈哈 没错
Ha ha! Yeah!
你们太慢了
You guys are too slow!
嘿
Hey!
哦! 哦! 哦!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
嗯 春日般清新
Mm, springtime fresh.
喔吼
Whoo-hoo!
啊 老下水道枢纽
Ah, the old drainage junction.
我的孩子们在哪儿?
Now where are my sons?